[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Shatner starred in this 1977 movie about a vet investigating the mysterious deaths of some farm animals.", "correct_answer": "Kingdom of The Spiders", "incorrect_answers": ["Ants", "Aberration", "Arachnophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two cards are randomly selected from a regular 52-card deck. What are the odds that they are both red?", "correct_answer": "25 out of 102", "incorrect_answers": ["1 in 4", "1 in 2", "1 in 26"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fictional character Jack Ryan tells Captain Ramius that he isnt a Navy officer and that he writes books for the CIA. He tells Ramius that he is the author of which of these books?", "correct_answer": "The Fighting Sailor", "incorrect_answers": ["History of the United States Navy", "Soviet Naval Tactics", "Pearl Harbor: Lessons of a Tragedy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1956, Tennessee businessman David Flexer had this great idea.", "correct_answer": "Show movies on airline flights", "incorrect_answers": ["Have airlines transport packages on long  flights", "Build a supersonic airplane", "Have floatation devices aboard airline flights"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The thriller The Happening stars John Leguizamo, Zoey Dechanel and this former member of Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch.", "correct_answer": "Mark Wahlberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Scott Tracy", "Donnie Gee", "Donnie Wahlberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for his performance in the 1997 movie Good Will Hunting?", "correct_answer": "Robin Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Casey Affleck", "Ben Affleck", "Matt Damon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What aristocratic title does Audrey Hepburns character have in the 1953 romantic comedy Roman Holiday?", "correct_answer": "A princess", "incorrect_answers": ["A countess", "A duchess", "A queen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetables are used for the making of the traditional Native American meal called Llapingacho?", "correct_answer": "Potatoes", "incorrect_answers": ["Toamtoes", "Peppers", "Carrots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only actor from the original Star Trek show to be in Star Trek XI?", "correct_answer": "Leonard Nimoy", "incorrect_answers": ["William Shatner", "Walter Koenig", "Nichelle Nichols"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Hunt for Red October, Seaman Jones, the sonar expert on the American submarine sent to track the Red October, was a student at what university before joining the Navy?", "correct_answer": "Cal Tech", "incorrect_answers": ["M.I.T.", "Stanford", "Yale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of the movies listed below did Steven Spielberg win Oscars for Best Director?", "correct_answer": "Schindlers List and Saving Private Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Schindlers List and The Color Purple", "Amistad and The Color Purple", "Empire of the Sun and Schindlers List"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was Nicole Kidman born?", "correct_answer": "Honolulu", "incorrect_answers": ["Perth", "Wellington", "Sydney"]}]